A Finding Aid to the W.G. Constable Papers, 1905-1983, bulk 1920-1976, in the Archives of American Art AAA.conswmgp
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Materials, circa 1940-1960; Series 10; 1.4 Linear feet Box 24-27, OV 28-29
  - Photographs of Fogg Art Museum, Interiors, circa 1940-1960 (Box 24, Folder 48-49)
  - Photographs of Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA) Dams, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Negatives of Artwork Reproduced from Nitrate Film, circa 1940 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Artwork and Architecture, Miscellaneous, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Artwork for Consideration, A-M, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4-7)
  - Photographs of Artwork for Consideration, N-Z, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
  - Photographs of Artwork for Consideration, Miscellaneous, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Artwork for Consideration, Unidentified, circa 1940-1960 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Oversized material housed in Box 28, Folder 8.
  - Glass Negatives of Artwork, circa 1940 (Box 26)
    23 glass plate negatives
  - Glass Negatives of Artwork, Boxes, circa 1940 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Glass Slides of Artwork, Architecture, circa 1940 (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
  - Glass Slides of Artwork, Paintings, circa 1940 (Box 27, Folder 6-11)
  - Glass Slides of Artwork, Sculpture, circa 1940 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Oversize Photographs, Photographs of Artwork for Consideration, Unidentified, circa 1940-1960 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Oversized material from Box 25, Folder 12.